althea.kr 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information Althea Inc. ("we" or "us") collects and how we use that information.

Overview

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use. By accepting the Althea Inc.’s Terms of Use when registering to receive services from Althea Inc. ("Althea"), you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. However, if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use Althea Services and do not access the Althea website located at www.althea.kr ("Althea Site").

This policy is effective from 06/01/2015. If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [help@althea.kr](mailto:help@althea.kr).

Information Collected

We collect, store and process your personal information on servers located in Korea. If you choose to use Althea Services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the Althea Site. Once you register or purchase products on the Althea Site, you are no longer anonymous to us.

We collect and store the following information:

Email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) financial information; computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Althea Site and ad data (all through cookies - You can take steps to disable cookies on your browser, however this is likely to affect your ability to use Althea Site); board posts and other messages, including correspondence between Althea and you; and general information regarding the Althea Services you have registered to.

We use your personal information to:

1\. Provide Althea Services and products;  
2\. Resolve disputes, calculate and collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;  
3\. Verify your identity and the information you provide;  
4\. Encourage a safe online experience and enforce our policies;  
5\. Customize your experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services, and inform you about services and updates;  
6\. Communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide you with information that may affect your use of Althea Services and products;  
7\. Communicate marketing and promotional offers to users;  
8\. Provide customer service; and  
9\. Perform other business activities as described when we collect the information.

During the course of the business, we may use your personal information to deliver to you information that is targeted to your interests. Upon receipt of the first communication of this type, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of future communications by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link or by following the "Unsubscribe" instructions described within the communication. From time to time, we may implement solutions designed to more efficiently capture your communications preferences. In any such event, we will strive to reflect any previously stated communicated preferences within such solutions. As part of your registration for Althea Services on the Althea Site, you agree that you may receive certain administrative communications from Althea, such as administrative announcements and customer service messages regarding Althea Services and products, and you will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications.

Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content is in violations of other's rights, or to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with:

1\. Corporate affiliates to help coordinate the services we provide to you; enforce our terms and conditions; and to promote trust and safety;  
2\. Service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of Althea Services to our users. These service providers are under confidentiality agreements with us;  
3\. Law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, to prevent, or to take action on illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law; and  
4\. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this Privacy Policy will continue to apply unless it is amended as described in "Notification of Changes" section set forth below.

Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

If you have registered to receive Althea Services, you can access, review and modify your personal information at any time by logging into your account page on the Althea Site. If you post messages using message boards or other messaging tools that may be made available on the Althea Site, it will not be possible to edit or delete those messages later. You may contact us at [help@althea.kr](mailto:help@althea.kr) to review any personal information we store about you that is not available on the Althea Site. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we have described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies, and to prevent unlawful or otherwise malicious abuse of our service.

To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools (encryption technologies, passwords, physical and electronic security, procedural safeguards) to assist in the protection of your information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the internet, so we make no guarantees.

Notification of Changes

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Althea Site. In the event of an amendment, all terms shall become effective 30 days after they are initially posted to the Althea Site. Your continued use of Althea Services, systems, and network will constitute your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy.

Our Address

Althea Inc.  
Ansun Building B02  
213 Yeongdong-daero, Gangnam-gu  
Seoul, South Korea  
135-501
